[theme music playing]
[tense music playing]
[screaming]
[shattering sound]
Can I ask you a favor?
I want to call you Mama.
[Helena] But, of course. Baby girl.
[Anna] Do you know someone
who wants to help Lily?
-Natalie.
-Are you serious, Jepoy?
You actually trust that woman?
[Jepoy] You're so convinced that someone
like Arnaldo can change.
But now that Natalie wants to
help us, you think it's wrong.
The arms shipment with Mr. Yi
will push through.
[Helena] And this is how Helena Montoya
becomes Red Dragon.
[Mercedes] If you don't show up
to the operation later,
this bullet will lodge itself in the head
of your beloved Camia.
[Lily] Red Dragon is making
a shipment tonight.
[Diego] I'll sabotage their delivery.
[Lily] Mom, I have to find a way
to help Diego's plan succeed.
[Julio] Where is your mother?
I thought she was dropping by for dinner.
I'm not expecting this family
to ever become whole again.
Mama doesn't need you.
Just because I'm not governor right now,
doesn't mean you can
treat me like an old rag!
[Romulo] Go ahead, Jaguar. Load it up.
Come back with
the money at exactly 10:00 p.m.
Make sure it's the exact amount.
[Romulo] I'll go with you.
You don't know where to deliver the goods.
Just leave it to me.
-If you really know, tell us.
-That's not necessary.
You know what to do with him.
Don't let him escape!
Oh, here's an update.
-[phone ringing]
-[Lily] Didn't we say no phones?
We said no such things.
You can ignore your own daughter,
but not me.
Not me.
Then, who?
[tense music playing]
[laughs]
Never mind.
[grunts]
[groans]
But I did notice that Emilia's
insecurities are getting worse.
Maybe you need to give her some attention.
I don't think I'm closer to you
than I am to my daughter.
Believe me or not, I'm just concerned.
[phone chimes]
[gasps]
IT'S DONE.
[sighs]
No phones.
[chuckles]
But, like what you said,
you're not young anymore.
And you have other matters
to attend to, right?
Well then. Um… Let's call it a night.
Yes.
Good night, Mama.
Good night, Lily.
[suspenseful music playing]
[birds chirping]
What's this? Why is there a truck here?
Sir!
There's a truck blocking the way.
Let's check it out.
Red Dragon?
It's unlocked.
Toledo! Tabang! Hurry and open this truck!
[locks clicking]
Check those boxes.
Sir, these are guns!
Check everything! Check everything!
[Lily] Were you able to bring
the shipment to the police?
The shipment is in
the police's custody now.
[Diego] And soon enough…
they'll be raiding the warehouse.
Lily, I also found something
that we can use against Red Dragon.
That would be a big help
to taking Helena Montoya down.
But Diego, how did you do it?
What did you do to get
into Red Dragon's hideout?
You'll find out soon. For now,
the important thing is,
we take Red Dragon down.
[tense music playing]
Sir, positive!
[Angelie on TV] More than a
thousand guns, including rifles
and other firearms amounting
to over 50 million pesos
are in police custody after being seized
from a shipment made by Red Dragon.
As of now, the police are trying to unmask
the identity of Red Dragon,
who is facing charges
of illegal arms trade and trafficking.
It can be recalled that Red Dragon is
also wanted for child prostitution.
[infuriated scream]
[screaming]
Now, the police know that
Red Dragon is active
not just here in Ardiente,
but in the whole country.
Mom, it's not enough
that the shipment was sabotaged.
The woman behind it needs to pay.
Helena Montoya must pay.
-[panting]
-[Mercedes] Madam.
Madam, it was an inside job.
I'll prove it to you.
[slow tense music playing]
Prove what? That it's you?
You're the reason the shipment failed!
Mercedes, you know how
many people this pin has killed.
Madam, please! It wasn't me!
It was Jaguar.
The Jaguar double-crossed us.
[dramatic music playing]
[Lily] I'll expose Helena Montoya.
I'll reveal that she's Red Dragon.
After what Diego did,
I'll release the documents
I got out of Mercedes Palacio's laptop.
The evidence you got from Club Dragonfly
will also help the case.
That's right, Mom.
And we need a witness to catch
Helena Montoya in the act.
[suspenseful music playing]
She forgets that gold can change form.
It gets even harder when exposed to fire.
So bring it on, Helena Montoya.
Let's see how great Red Dragon really is.
Because I'm here to slay you.
[tense music playing]
The Jaguar betrayed me?
[grunts]
[slow tense music playing]
Find the Jaguar! Now!
Didn't I tell you never to call me here?
[Damian's henchman]
But, Boss, we have a problem.
The shipment was raided last night.
The police have our guns.
It's on the news.
[henchman] I'm sure
Red Dragon's pissed right now.
Knowing her, whoever failed her
will be burned alive.
[panting]
What were you thinking?
Why'd you wear that mask?
I went to Red Dragon's hideout
so I could stop their operations.
Do you know what you're doing?
Do you hear yourself, Diego?
You think this is right?!
Sorry for putting your life
in danger, Dad.
But no matter what happens,
I'll do whatever it takes
to stop Red Dragon and all her plans.
[scoffs]
Don't worry about me, son.
You should worry about yourself.
After what you did, she'll
definitely come after you.
[ominous music playing]
[grunting]
[engine starts]
Madam Red Dragon,
I had nothing to do with that.
Don't lie to me.
If I'd been behind that mask,
would I come back here?
If that were the case,
shouldn't I be hiding from you?
I'm telling you,
I didn't sabotage the shipment.
If that wasn't you, then who was it?
Who?!
An imposter who goes around
and calls himself the Jaguar.
He was the one
who sabotaged your shipment.
Get out. Everybody get out!
[Helena] Hello. Finally.
Mercedes, I can't reach you
on your cellphone.
I've been trying to call you.
You need to report to me, ASAP.
[Helena] Hello, Mercedes. Can you hear me?
Then tell me. Who answered the phone?
Were you with someone?
Yes, Madam.
And I did not answer because I was wasted.
You're the reason why the shipment failed!
It wasn't me. It was Jaguar.
[Mercedes] The Jaguar double-crossed us.
I had nothing to do with that.
An imposter who goes around
and calls himself the Jaguar.
-Helena!
-It's different to me.
[Emilia] It's not just an act of kindness
that you see in Lily Cruz.
You know what she did to me before, Mama?
She almost took a bullet for my life.
She saved my life. Exactly the same thing
that she's doing to you right now, Mama.
See what kind of person
our little "friend" is?
I have three people of interest.
[tense music playing]
Mercedes.
Damian.
Lily Cruz.
And I know how to hit
all of them at the same time.
Diego.
Lily.
I'm sure Red Dragon
is looking for the person
who sabotaged her operation.
So please, be careful.
I think I made a mistake, Lily.
I pretended to be someone else
to infiltrate Red Dragon's hideout.
And because of that,
someone else might get hurt.
But you know me, Lily.
My whole life,
I've fought for what's right.
This is the only time
I've lied and stole--
Diego, wait, what are you talking about?
Sometimes, you have to do things…
you don't want to for the greater good.
I wish… I wish I'd done this sooner.
[pensive music playing]
I may not know what you're talking about,
but don't ever think
you're wrong for fighting
for what's right.
Diego, I've always admired you
for fighting for the truth.
I know you're a man of principles.
And, that's why I hope you never change.
I hope you never lose that integrity.
Damian, come here. Try this.
It's been Lily's favorite
since she was a kid.
I bet you'll like it too.
Yeah. It does look good.
Dig in.
Are you still thinking about
Red Dragon's failed operation?
Who do you think
could've foiled her plans?
Maybe it's one of her
own minions in the syndicate.
One of Red Dragon's minions?
Mom?
-Lily. Diego.
-Auntie.
You're just in time.
I just finished making some snacks.
-Wow!
-Come join us.
Sure. Diego and I are a bit hungry.
[phone ringing]
Sorry, hold on.
It's the dragon.
Helena?
Hi, Lily.
Yes. Need anything?
I called to invite you
to another bonding session.
I felt like the other night
ended too early.
Oh. I thought I was the only
one who thought that.
Well, I did say you could call
whenever you needed me.
So, what do you have in mind? Dinner?
Better.
[suspenseful music playing]
Oh, hey Anna.
So, did you tell Jepoy you love him?
I'm too afraid to tell him.
I don't want to get hurt.
Anna, relax. Being in love isn't wrong.
Why? Have you ever been in love?
I hope so.
I mean, it feels so good to be in love.
Especially when you're
with the one who matters.
Just the two of you, talking…
laughing…
Just being together.
Holding each other, embracing.
Hugging them tight.
[ominous music playing]
You hold them tight, because…
you always want them by your side.
And, you'll hug them even tighter
so that they'll never leave.
You'll keep them with
you because they're yours.
[chokes] Arnaldo.
They're all yours and you don't
want anyone else to have them!
Stop it Arnaldo!
Why were you trying to choke me?!
[tense music playing]
No, I…
[panting]
[tense music playing]
We're done, ma'am.
Thank you.
I told you my masseuse
was fabulous, right?
[ominous music playing]
Helena?
Do you know what this is?
[Lily] Ah!
It could be painful but
it could also give you pleasure.
It could also be deadly.
Especially if you prick
the death spot at the back of the neck.
It would lead to oxygen
deprivation, and then, death.
So, Lily, why don't we play a little game?
All you have to do is answer
as truthfully as you can.
Are you ready?
Can I trust you?
Ouch!
Yes!
Do you trust me?
Or are you wary of me?
Are we really friends?
Helena.
If we really are friends…
are you willing to risk
your life for a friend?
[suspenseful music playing]
Ah!
Ouch. [chuckling]
Lily, I was just kidding.
Kidding?
Hmm.
You're just like your daughter, Emilia.
Well then Mama,
the answer to all your
questions is a solid yes.
Because I know the person I'm talking to
isn't hiding anything from me.
Right, Mama?
Right?! Mama!
[suspenseful music playing]
Say yes.
Yes.
Very good, Mama.
You know what, Mama?
I have eyes watching you
even when I'm away.
I already know about your plans,
even before you come up with them.
So, don't you even dare, Mama.
[tense music playing]
Are you okay, Mama?
-Yeah.
-Let me help you.
Hmm… So relaxing.
[Lily] I've spoken to
Attorney Fisher, Mom.
There's an investigator
on Helena Montoya's trail.
What do you think?
Do you think she knows that
you're aware of her true identity?
It doesn't matter, Mom.
But she can't kill me
because I'm the one
who keeps her name clean.
Lily, what are you planning?
The fight continues, Mom.
But this time, I'll stick
even closer to that woman
until I catch her in the act.
Mama.
How was your bonding with Lily Cruz?
Am I going to have someone buried soon?
Yes, but not Lily. She's still an asset.
And we can't just kill her
without sufficient proof
that she's involved in the sabotage.
How about Jaguar?
He's the one on the CCTV footage.
Should we really believe what he said?
That an imposter took the shipment?
Wait, Mama.
Are you trying to say
that Jaguar is now a suspect?
Yes.
Mercedes, find someone skilled enough
to take care of the Jaguar.
Wait, Mama.
Jaguar is my friend.
Yes, Mama, he's been my long-time friend
and he was there for me
during my dark days.
So, please. Mama, don't hurt him.
Are we talking about the same Jaguar?
[Diego] Dad.
[crickets chirping]
I'm glad we got to spend time together.
And thank you.
Thank you for always protecting me.
[pensive music playing]
I always will, son.
Thank you too for saving my life.
But please…
I don't want you wearing this mask again.
-But, Dad…
-This isn't for you, son.
I can use it for the greater good
and to take down Red Dragon.
If Red Dragon's all you're worried about,
fine, I'll help you.
I'll help you investigate her.
But like I said,
don't ever use this again.
Do you understand?
Mama, my friend, Jaguar, told me that
there are two Jaguars.
One of them is a copycat.
Yes, but I'm pretty sure
that the Jaguar I know
is the real one.
[sighs]
So, instead of investigating Lily,
why don't you try to investigate
your Jaguar friend?
Okay, Mama.
I will talk to my Jaguar friend.
But please, don't stop me
from investigating Lily Cruz.
I know that woman very well.
She has messed up
my family countless times.
And I don't want the same thing
to happen to you, Mama.
Do we have a deal now?
Yes, we have a deal.
Lily, please don't take this
the wrong way…
but isn't there another way
to take Helena Montoya down?
Mom…
Do you want me
to stop getting close to her?
Lily, I'm trying.
But I can't forget how the
Ardientes captured you before.
That won't ever happen again, Mom.
I always take care of myself
because I don't want us
to be separated again.
Because your life
is as important as mine, Mom.
So, I'm taking care of myself.
I promise I'll always be careful.
[phone chimes]
I HAVE PROOF THAT HELENA MONTOYA
IS RED DRAGON.
Is something wrong?
It's an anonymous text, Mom.
It says they have proof
Helena Montoya is Red Dragon.
Red Dragon's identity remains
a mystery to the public.
She's allegedly connected
to child prostitution--
Red Dragon.
…and illegal trafficking
of high-powered arms.
Jaguar. Why didn't I think
of an alias for myself?
What would be a cheesy, nice alias?
The Roaring Lion.
The Kingpin.
The Leviathan.
Killer Shark.
Handsome Devil.
Nah.
Sounds too narcissistic.
Reports say that even
the police find it difficult
to chase down the said criminal.
Everyone is advised to remain
vigilant against the
group's modus operandi,
which is said to be rampant.
This is Angelie Berlin, reporting.
[scoffs]
I got news for you, news people.
I haven't just been beside her.
I've even slept with the enemy.
And she found me delicious.
[laughing]
Oh my, Helena.
You're a puzzle.
Sir.
-Yeah?
-You have a visitor.
Missing me already, Julio Ardiente?
[tense music playing]
Helena, what do you want?
Why are you here in my house again?
Emilia told me you were asking
her when I was available.
Well, I'm available now.
I must admit I missed you.
Although, I'm not prepared now.
You know when I was prepared?
[jazz music playing]
A couple of days ago.
When you didn't show up.
Before you get any ideas,
I thought this is just a friendly meeting.
Well, I'm here now.
But you know what?
I'm feeling tired. So, I'm going to bed.
You're sleeping over?
Yeah. Why? Is there a problem?
No, no, no. I can have
the maids change my bedsheets.
Satin pink.
Don't be silly. I'm going
to be using the guest room.
In fact, my bags are already there.
The guest room is musky, Helena.
Really?
-Yes.
-It's musky?
Then I better take a shower
so that I will stay fresh.
-Goodnight.
-The shower's in my room.
It's big, it's large, it's sexy.
I'm still staying in the guest room.
Good night, Julio. You silly old cow.
-Silly old cow, my foot!
-[door closes]
Who could the sender be?
Who else knows that you know that
Red Dragon and Helena Montoya
are the same person?
It's nice to know there's a helping hand.
Though I have no idea who that person is.
But don't worry, Mom.
I'll figure this one out.
I'll get back to you.
For now, you should rest.
Okay, then.
-Good night, Mom.
-Good night.
I HAVE PROOF THAT HELENA MONTOYA
IS RED DRAGON.
Raul couldn't have done it.
[suspenseful music playing]
The last time I saw him,
he was shot in the stomach.
[Damian] I'll deal with that impostor!
But the Jaguar on the CCTV footage
didn't look like he was injured.
[suspenseful music playing]
-[grunts]
-[gunshots]
[Raul] Let Diego go!
Diego, run!
[Damian] I said, leave!
It's Diego.
Diego's pretending to be Jaguar.
[music swells]
-Nanny! Uncle!
-Oh! Diego!
-Nanny!
-Pandoy, Diego's here!
[Pandoy] Diego? Diego! Diego, son!
-Uncle!
-Diego, how are you?
Uncle!
Oh, my.
-Diego, what happened?
-You've been gone for days!
How are you?
-Right.
-What happened to you, Diego?
Good thing Lily always tells us
what you're up to.
Otherwise, your aunt
would've been so worried.
Nanny, Uncle, I told you
not to worry about me.
I can take care of myself.
[Loring laughs]
I just had to take care of something.
What?
Good morning, Mrs. Loring.
Good morning.
Dad, I know you didn't approve
of what I did.
But I want you to know
that I don't regret it.
Son, you don't have to explain anything.
I understand.
And I respect your decision.
I'm just here to support you.
Thanks, Dad.
[Loring and Pandoy laugh]
We have no idea what you're talking about.
Yep. She's right.
It looks like they're getting along.
If you're happy, Diego, then
Pandoy and I are happy for you.
That's true.
We may not get what's going on,
but I guess it sounded like a good thing.
[Loring and Pandoy laughing]
Nanny, I'm always happy when I'm with you.
I've missed you so much.
-We missed you too.
-Come here, you two.
[Pandoy laughing]
You have such a bright smile on you.
[Emilia] So you're the fake Jaguar?
I need to speak to you. Answer the phone!
[line ringing]
This is really important.
I need you to pick up the phone.
[line ringing]
[grunts]
Raul. Don't tell me you just got home.
Well, so much for you acting like a wife.
I've been gone for days
and you just noticed?
Wait, did Mama see you?
Your mother's here?
Yeah. And she cannot see you like this.
You need to take a bath.
You need to shave.
Oh my God, you need to take a shower.
She cannot see you like this, Raul.
Good morning, Julio.
It is indeed a beautiful morning.
Did you sleep well?
Not as much as I would've loved to.
But it is indeed a beautiful morning.
You know what would really be
an ideal good morning
for the two of us?
It's us not having to come
out of different rooms
in the morning meeting each other halfway,
but coming out of one single room…
[jazz music playing]
after a memorable night.
Now that, I would dare say, is perfection.
-Oh, you silly cow.
-The silly cow still has it.
Or have you forgotten?
But, as much as I would like to join you,
I have some pressing engagements
that I have to attend to this morning.
My lady, I have to go.
-Sir.
-Hi.
Good mood? You look inspired.
I'm in a very, very good mood.
And I am very inspired.
Before this day is done, Colonel,
I will show you that Julio Ardiente
is still king of the province of Ardiente.
[ominous music playing]
That governor position?
[scoffs]
It's going to be crawling back to me,
like a jilted lover
begging for a second chance,
pleading to be loved.
Watch and learn, Colonel.
[scoffs]
Goodbye, my love.
Farewell.
[Julio laughs softly]
[Julio] Ah…
Sir, our men are with one of the witnesses
of Camia's shooting.
It's a good thing we have an early start.
Too many people saw me shoot Camia.
Typical Filipinos. So nosy. Oh.
Good morning, Teacher Liza.
Good morning. What do you want?
What are you going to do to me?
Please don't kill me.
[sobbing]
Is that really how you think of me?
Do I look like a murderer?
I'm just here to talk.
[sighs]
Here's 50,000 pesos, Teacher Liza.
All that I ask is for you
not to testify against me…
in the case of Camia Cruz's shooting.
Huh?
Take it.
An act of kindness
from one neighbor to another.
By the way, before I forget.
Um… The other reason
why I'm here is to ask you
if you can help me find these people.
[suspenseful music playing]
Today is a very, very good day
because today,
you will expose Lily Cruz as your enemy.
And I already hired a private investigator
and all the surprises.
Mama?
Yeah. That's great. That's great.
Mama, I still haven't spoken
to my friend, Jaguar.
[Helena] Well, when you do talk
to him, that's when we'll know
whether or not he was the one
who sabotaged my shipment.
[suspenseful music playing]
Hey! Who's there?!
Look, someone hiding there.
Who on earth is that?
Why don't you show your face?!
Get down from there.
Sorry, I just took care
of something at the back.
Mama, that's my husband Raul.
Raul, come. Join us.
How are you, Mama?
Humor me, how did a lazy-eyed
moose like you, of all people,
end up marrying my one and only daughter?
Mama.
Well, what do you do?
I have a… I run a small jewelry business.
Emilia, I didn't know
you had a thing for peasants.
Mama!
It's not like that--
I've heard enough. It's okay.
Sit down. Join us.
[Emilia] Eat.
Mrs. Loring! Mister Pandoy!
Mrs. Liza?
Nanny! Uncle! It's Mrs. Liza!
Hey, Liza.
Good day to you.
Oh, Liza!
[Liza] Ah…
Mrs. Loring.
Mister Pandoy.
Mrs. Liza, is there a problem?
Diego…
Julio Ardiente approached me earlier.
[suspenseful music playing]
Ms. Dang, Nikki,
please watch over the stove.
-Yes, ma'am.
-Thank you.
Lily.
I feel like someone's watching us, Mom.
Lily, don't you think
you're just being paranoid?
I'm sorry, Mom.
But as long as our enemies are alive,
I'll never be at peace.
And, that's why
I'm going to meet up
with our anonymous informant.
They might be able to help us
corner Red Dragon.
Just keep your eyes open, okay?
This could be a trap.
Don't just put your trust in them.
I'm sorry, Mom,
but I'll still take that risk.
And that's because I'm done playing games
with Red Dragon.
I've lost my patience.
[Julio] This is for you.
Just don't testify
that you saw me shoot Camia--
[Diego] And what do we have here?!
[Julio] Excuse me.
You just can't accept defeat, can you?
[Julio laughs]
Of course!
An Ardiente never accepts defeat or loses.
An Ardiente will never
just let this thing sli--
So, you're threatening and bribing
Aunt Camia's witnesses against you,
now that your 90-day suspension
is almost over!
-Yes.
-I know what you're up to.
You're cleaning up all the mess
that can prevent you
from returning to power.
But what makes you so sure
that you can ever return?!
Diego, for an Ardiente like me,
politics is like a very long plane ride.
You'll be flying high for hours
and hours until the plane
descends from the sky
to land for refueling.
After which,
it will take to the skies again
for another long journey.
At this point, I have refueled, Diego,
so I won't stay on the ground any longer.
I'm ready to soar once more.
You're all talk.
I'll make sure
that this is your last ride!
[tense music playing]
You know what?
I will never be stopped
by a loser like you!
Sir!
Don't kid yourself.
You only won because you cheated!
You bastard!
Sir.
-Sir… Sir?
-[Julio grunts]
Remember, Julio.
As long as I'm alive,
you'll never be
the governor of this province.
Remember that!
[tense music playing]
This is a clone of Mercedes' phone.
[Jepoy] You can keep track
of all her calls
and text messages from here.
[Camia] It's confirmed.
That's another piece of evidence
that will prove
that Helena Montoya is Red Dragon.
[Diego] I've waited so long
to give you this.
I love you so much.
[Anna] Why are you so happy?
[Arnaldo] I think I saw an angel.
Is she my brother's girlfriend?
[Jepoy] What if the old Arnaldo
comes back?
The cruel Arnaldo. Are we still
going to protect him?
[Anna] If that does happen, Jepoy,
are you going to kill him?
Yes. Without a doubt.
Jepoy!
[theme music playing]